<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="term_of_service"><![CDATA[
Terms of Use

Last updated on March 9, 2020

These terms and conditions ("Terms", "Agreement") are an agreement between Mobile Application Developer ("Mobile Application Developer", "us", "we" or "our") and you ("User", "you" or "your"). This Agreement sets forth the general terms and conditions of your use of the Tripals mobile application and any of its products or services (collectively, "Mobile Application" or "Services").

Scope of Services
The Tripals Platform is an online marketplace that enables registered users (“Members”) and certain third parties who offer single or multi-day activities in various categories (“Events”) (Members and third parties who offer Events are “Hosts”) to publish such Events on the Tripals Platform (“Listings”) and to communicate directly with Members that are seeking to join such Events (Members joining Events are “Participants”). Tripals does not own, create, sell, resell, provide, control, manage, offer, deliver, or supply any Listings. Hosts alone are responsible for their Listings and Events. When Members make or accept a booking, they are entering into a contract directly with each other. Tripals is not and does not become a party to or other participant in any contractual relationship between Members. Tripals is not acting as an agent in any capacity for any Member. While we may help facilitate the resolution of disputes, Tripals has no control over and does not guarantee (i) the existence, quality, safety, suitability, or legality of any Events, (ii) the truth or accuracy of any Listing descriptions, Ratings, Reviews, or other Member Content, or (iii) the performance or conduct of any Member or third party. Tripals does not endorse any Member, Listing or Events. You should always exercise due diligence and care when deciding whether to participate in an Event, accept a booking request from a Participant, or communicate and interact with other Members, whether online or in person. If you choose to use the Tripals platform as a Host, your relationship with Tripals is limited to being an independent, third-party contractor, and not an employee, agent, joint venturer or partner of Tripals for any reason, and you act exclusively on your own behalf and for your own benefit, and not on behalf, or for the benefit, of Tripals. Tripals does not, and shall not be deemed to, direct or control you generally or in your performance under these Terms specifically, including in connection with your provision of the Events. You acknowledge and agree that you have complete discretion whether to list Events or otherwise engage in other business or employment activities.

Accounts and membership
You must be at least 13 years of age to use this Mobile Application. By using this Mobile Application and by agreeing to this Agreement you warrant and represent that you are at least 13 years of age. If you create an account in the Mobile Application, you are responsible for maintaining the security of your account and you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under the account and any other actions taken in connection with it. We may, but have no obligation to, monitor and review new accounts before you may sign in and use our Services. Providing false contact information of any kind may result in the termination of your account. You must immediately notify us of any unauthorized uses of your account or any other breaches of security. We will not be liable for any acts or omissions by you, including any damages of any kind incurred as a result of such acts or omissions. We may suspend, disable, or delete your account (or any part thereof) if we determine that you have violated any provision of this Agreement or that your conduct or content would tend to damage our reputation and goodwill. In addition, Tripals may take any of the following measures (i) to comply with applicable law, or the order or request of a court, law enforcement or other administrative agency or governmental body, or if (ii) you have breached these Terms, applicable laws, regulations, or third party rights, (iii) you have provided inaccurate, fraudulent, outdated or incomplete information during the Tripals Account registration, Listing process or thereafter, (iv) you and/or your Listings or Events at any time fail to meet any applicable quality or eligibility criteria, (v) you have repeatedly received poor Ratings or Reviews or Tripals otherwise becomes aware of or has received complaints about your performance or conduct, or (vi) Tripals believes in good faith that such action is reasonably necessary to protect the personal safety or property of Tripals, its Members, or third parties, or to prevent fraud or other illegal activity:
refuse to surface, delete or delay any Listings, Ratings, Reviews, or other Member Content;
cancel any pending or confirmed bookings;
limit your access to or use of the Tripals Platform;
temporarily or permanently revoke any special status associated with your Tripals Account;
temporarily or in case of severe or repeated offenses permanently suspend your Tripals Account and stop providing access to the Tripals Platform.
If we delete your account for the foregoing reasons, you may not re-register for our Services. We may block your email address and Internet protocol address to prevent further registration.

User content
We do not own any data, information or material ("Content") that you submit in the Mobile Application in the course of using the Service. You shall have sole responsibility for the accuracy, quality, integrity, legality, reliability, appropriateness, and intellectual property ownership or right to use of all submitted Content. We may, but have no obligation to, monitor and review Content in the Mobile Application submitted or created using our Services by you. Unless specifically permitted by you, your use of the Mobile Application does not grant us the license to use, reproduce, adapt, modify, publish or distribute the Content created by you or stored in your user account for commercial, marketing or any similar purpose. But you grant us permission to access, copy, distribute, store, transmit, reformat, display and perform the Content of your user account solely as required for the purpose of providing the Services to you. Without limiting any of those representations or warranties, we have the right, though not the obligation, to, in our own sole discretion, refuse or remove any Content that, in our reasonable opinion, violates any of our policies or is in any way harmful or objectionable.

Terms specific for Hosts
When creating a Listing through the Tripals Platform you must (i) provide complete and accurate information about your Events (such as listing description, location, and date), (ii) disclose any deficiencies, restrictions and requirements that apply (such as any minimum age, proficiency or fitness requirements) and (iii) provide any other pertinent information requested by Tripals. You are responsible for keeping your Listing information up-to-date at all times. Tripals reserves the right to decide, in its sole discretion, whether a submitted Event will be published on the Tripals Platform. You are responsible for acquiring all equipment, including supplies, vehicles, venues and other materials (“Equipment”) necessary to host your Event. You are solely responsible for ensuring that the Equipment used in your Event is in good working order and conforms to all laws pertaining to safety, equipment, inspection, and operational capability. Except as otherwise required by law, you assume all risk of damage or loss to your Equipment. You are responsible for (i) understanding and complying with all laws, rules and regulations that may apply to your Event(s), (ii) obtaining any required licenses, permits, or registrations prior to providing your Event(s); and (iii) ensuring that your Listing and/or Hosting of an Event will not breach any agreement you may have with any third party.

Terms specific for Participants
You should carefully review the description of any Event you intend to book to ensure you meet any minimum age, proficiency, fitness or other requirements which the Host has specified in their Listing. At your sole discretion you may want to inform the Host of any medical or physical conditions, or other circumstances that may impact your ability to participate in any Event. In addition, certain laws, like the minimum legal drinking age in the location of the Event, may also apply. You are responsible for identifying, understanding, and complying with all laws, rules and regulations that apply to your participation in an Event. Before and during an Event you must at all times adhere to the Hosts’ instructions.

Booking Modification and Cancellations
Hosts and Participants are responsible for any modifications to a booking that they make via the Tripals Platform ("Booking Modifications"). If weather poses a safety risk to Participants, or if it prevents a Host from carrying out an Event that takes place primarily outdoors, Hosts may cancel the Event. Hosts may also cancel the Event if other conditions exist that would prevent the Host from offering the Event safely.

Ratings and Reviews
Within a certain timeframe after completing a booking, Participants and Hosts can leave a public review (“Review”) and submit a star rating (“Rating”) about each other. Ratings or Reviews reflect the opinions of individual Members and do not reflect the opinion of Tripals. Ratings and Reviews are not verified by Tripals for accuracy and may be incorrect or misleading. Ratings and Reviews by Participants and Hosts must be accurate and may not contain any offensive or defamatory language. Members are prohibited from manipulating the Ratings and Reviews system in any manner, such as instructing a third party to write a positive or negative Review about another Member. Ratings and Reviews are part of a Member’s public profile and may also be surfaced elsewhere on the Tripals Platform (such as the Listing page) together with other relevant information.

Backups
We perform regular backups of the Content, however, these backups are for our own administrative purposes only and are in no way guaranteed. You are responsible for maintaining your own backups of your data. We do not provide any sort of compensation for lost or incomplete data in the event that backups do not function properly. We will do our best to ensure complete and accurate backups, but assume no responsibility for this duty.

Links to other mobile applications
Some areas of the Tripals platform implement Google Maps services, including Google Maps API(s). Your use of Google Maps is subject to the Google Maps/Google Earth Additional Terms of Service (https://www.google.com/help/terms_maps/). Although this Mobile Application may link to other mobile applications, we are not, directly or indirectly, implying any approval, association, sponsorship, endorsement, or affiliation with any linked mobile application, unless specifically stated herein. We are not responsible for examining or evaluating, and we do not warrant the offerings of, any businesses or individuals or the content of their mobile applications. We do not assume any responsibility or liability for the actions, products, services, and content of any other third-parties. You should carefully review the legal statements and other conditions of use of any mobile application which you access through a link from this Mobile Application. Your linking to any other off-site mobile applications is at your own risk.

Prohibited uses
In addition to other terms as set forth in the Agreement, you are prohibited from using the Mobile Application or its Content: (a) for any unlawful purpose; (b) to solicit others to perform or participate in any unlawful acts; (c) to violate any international, federal, provincial or state regulations, rules, laws, or local ordinances; (d) to infringe upon or violate our intellectual property rights or the intellectual property rights of others; (e) to harass, abuse, insult, harm, defame, slander, disparage, intimidate, or discriminate based on gender, sexual orientation, religion, ethnicity, race, age, national origin, or disability; (f) to submit false or misleading information; (g) to upload or transmit viruses or any other type of malicious code that will or may be used in any way that will affect the functionality or operation of the Service or of any related mobile application, other mobile applications, or the Internet; (h) to collect or track the personal information of others; (i) to spam, phish, pharm, pretext, spider, crawl, or scrape; (j) for any obscene or immoral purpose; or (k) to interfere with or circumvent the security features of the Service or any related mobile application, other mobile applications, or the Internet. We reserve the right to terminate your use of the Service or any related mobile application for violating any of the prohibited uses. You acknowledge that Tripals has no obligation to monitor the access to or use of the Tripals Platform by any Member or to review, disable access to, or edit any Member Content, but has the right to do so to (i) operate, secure and improve the Tripals Platform (including without limitation for fraud prevention, risk assessment, investigation and customer support purposes); (ii) ensure Members’ compliance with these Terms; (iii) comply with applicable law or the order or requirement of a court, law enforcement or other administrative agency or governmental body; (iv) respond to Member Content that it determines is harmful or objectionable; or (v) as otherwise set forth in these Terms. Members agree to cooperate with and assist Tripals in good faith, and to provide Tripals with such information and take such actions as may be reasonably requested by Tripals with respect to any investigation undertaken by Tripals or a representative of Tripals regarding the use or abuse of the Tripals Platform. If you feel that any Member you interact with, whether online or in person, is acting or has acted inappropriately, including but not limited to anyone who (i) engages in offensive, violent or sexually inappropriate behavior, (ii) you suspect of stealing from you, or (iii) engages in any other disturbing conduct, you should immediately report such person to the appropriate authorities and then to Tripals by contacting us with your police station and report number (if available). You agree that any report you make will not obligate us to take any action (beyond that required by law, if any).

Intellectual property rights
This Agreement does not transfer to you any intellectual property owned by Mobile Application Developer or third-parties, and all rights, titles, and interests in and to such property will remain (as between the parties) solely with Mobile Application Developer. All trademarks, service marks, graphics and logos used in connection with our Mobile Application or Services, are trademarks or registered trademarks of Mobile Application Developer or Mobile Application Developer licensors. Other trademarks, service marks, graphics and logos used in connection with our Mobile Application or Services may be the trademarks of other third-parties. Your use of our Mobile Application and Services grants you no right or license to reproduce or otherwise use any Mobile Application Developer or third-party trademarks.

Disclaimers
If you choose to use the Tripals Platform or its Content, you do so voluntarily and at your sole risk. The Tripals Platform and its Content is provided “as is”, without warranty of any kind, either express or implied. You agree that you have had whatever opportunity you deem necessary to investigate the Tripals Services, laws, rules, or regulations that may be applicable to your Listings and/or Events you are receiving and that you are not relying upon any statement of law or fact made by Tripals relating to a Listing. You agree that some Events may carry inherent risk, and by participating in such services, you choose to assume those risks voluntarily. You assume full responsibility for the choices you make before, during and after your participation in an Event. The foregoing disclaimers apply to the maximum extent permitted by law. You may have other statutory rights. However, the duration of statutorily required warranties, if any, shall be limited to the maximum extent permitted by law.

Limitation of liability
To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, in no event will Mobile Application Developer, its affiliates, officers, directors, employees, agents, suppliers or licensors be liable to any person for (a): any indirect, incidental, special, punitive, cover or consequential damages (including, without limitation, damages for lost profits, revenue, sales, goodwill, use of content, impact on business, business interruption, loss of anticipated savings, loss of business opportunity) however caused, under any theory of liability, including, without limitation, contract, tort, warranty, breach of statutory duty, negligence or otherwise, even if Mobile Application Developer has been advised as to the possibility of such damages or could have foreseen such damages. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, the aggregate liability of Mobile Application Developer and its affiliates, officers, employees, agents, suppliers and licensors, relating to the services will be limited to an amount greater of one dollar or any amounts actually paid in cash by you to Mobile Application Developer for the prior one month period prior to the first event or occurrence giving rise to such liability. The limitations and exclusions also apply if this remedy does not fully compensate you for any losses or fails of its essential purpose.

Indemnification
You agree to indemnify and hold Mobile Application Developer and its affiliates, directors, officers, employees, and agents harmless from and against any liabilities, losses, damages or costs, including reasonable attorneys\' fees, incurred in connection with or arising from any third-party allegations, claims, actions, disputes, or demands asserted against any of them as a result of or relating to your Content, your use of the Mobile Application or Services or any willful misconduct on your part.

Severability
All rights and restrictions contained in this Agreement may be exercised and shall be applicable and binding only to the extent that they do not violate any applicable laws and are intended to be limited to the extent necessary so that they will not render this Agreement illegal, invalid or unenforceable. If any provision or portion of any provision of this Agreement shall be held to be illegal, invalid or unenforceable by a court of competent jurisdiction, it is the intention of the parties that the remaining provisions or portions thereof shall constitute their agreement with respect to the subject matter hereof, and all such remaining provisions or portions thereof shall remain in full force and effect.

Dispute resolution
The formation, interpretation, and performance of this Agreement and any disputes arising out of it shall be governed by the substantive and procedural laws of Hong Kong without regard to its rules on conflicts or choice of law and, to the extent applicable, the laws of Hong Kong. The exclusive jurisdiction and venue for actions related to the subject matter hereof shall be the courts located in Hong Kong, and you hereby submit to the personal jurisdiction of such courts. You hereby waive any right to a jury trial in any proceeding arising out of or related to this Agreement. The United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods does not apply to this Agreement.

Changes and amendments
We reserve the right to modify this Agreement or its policies relating to the Mobile Application or Services at any time, effective upon posting of an updated version of this Agreement in the Mobile Application. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the top of this page. Continued use of the Mobile Application after any such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes.

Acceptance of these terms
You acknowledge that you have read this Agreement and agree to all its terms and conditions. By using the Mobile Application or its Services you agree to be bound by this Agreement. If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Agreement, you are not authorized to use or access the Mobile Application and its Services.

Contacting us
If you would like to contact us to understand more about this Agreement or wish to contact us concerning any matter relating to it, you may send an email to meetyourtripals@gmail.com


    ]]></string>
    <string name="privacy_policy"><![CDATA[
Privacy Policy

Last updated on March 9, 2020

This privacy policy ("Policy") describes how Mobile Application Developer ("Mobile Application Developer", "we", "us" or "our") collects, protects and uses the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you ("User", "you" or "your") may provide in the Tripals mobile application and any of its products or services (collectively, "Mobile Application" or "Services").

It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Information and how you can access and update this information. This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

Automatic collection of information
When you open the Mobile Application our servers automatically record information that your device sends. This data may include information such as your device\'s IP address and location, device name and version, operating system type and version, language preferences, information you search for in our Mobile Application, access times and dates, and other statistics.

Information collected automatically is used only to identify potential cases of abuse and establish statistical information regarding Mobile Application traffic and usage. This statistical information is not otherwise aggregated in such a way that would identify any particular user of the system.

Collection of personal information
You can visit the Mobile Application without telling us who you are or revealing any information by which someone could identify you as a specific, identifiable individual. If, however, you wish to use some of the Mobile Application\'s features, you will be asked to provide certain Personal Information (for example, your name and e-mail address). We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us when you create an account, publish content, or fill any online forms in the Mobile Application. When required, this information may include the following:
Personal details such as name, country of residence, etc.
Contact information such as email address, address, etc.
Account details such as user name, unique user ID, password, etc.
Geolocation data of the mobile device such as latitude and longitude.
Certain features on the mobile device such as contacts, calendar, gallery, etc.
Any other materials you willingly submit to us such as articles, images, feedback, etc.

You can choose not to provide us with your Personal Information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of some of the Mobile Application\'s features. Users who are uncertain about what information is mandatory are welcome to contact us.

Managing personal information
You are able to delete certain Personal Information we have about you. The Personal Information you can delete may change as the Mobile Application or Services change. When you delete Personal Information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised Personal Information in our records for the duration necessary to comply with our obligations to our affiliates and partners, and for the purposes described below. If you would like to delete your Personal Information or permanently delete your account, you can do so by contacting us.

Storing personal information
We will retain and use your Personal Information for the period necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. Once the retention period expires, Personal Information shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after the expiration of the retention period.

Use and processing of collected information
In order to make our Mobile Application and Services available to you, or to meet a legal obligation, we need to collect and use certain Personal Information. If you do not provide the information that we request, we may not be able to provide you with the requested products or services. Some of the information we collect is directly from you via our Mobile Application. However, we may also collect Personal Information about you from other sources. Any of the information we collect from you may be used for the following purposes:
Create and manage user accounts
Send administrative information
Respond to inquiries and offer support
Request user feedback
Improve user experience
Enforce terms and conditions and policies
Protect from abuse and malicious users
Respond to legal requests and prevent harm
Run and operate our Mobile Application and Services

Processing your Personal Information depends on how you interact with our Mobile Application, where you are located in the world and if one of the following applies: (i) You have given your consent for one or more specific purposes. This, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Information is subject to California Consumer Privacy Act or European data protection law; (ii) Provision of information is necessary for the performance of an agreement with you and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof; (iii) Processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which you are subject; (iv) Processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in us; (v) Processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party.

Note that under some legislations we may be allowed to process information until you object to such processing (by opting out), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases below. In any case, we will be happy to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Information is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.

Information transfer and storage
Depending on your location, data transfers may involve transferring and storing your information in a country other than your own. You are entitled to learn about the legal basis of information transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by us to safeguard your information. If any such transfer takes place, you can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this document or inquire with us using the information provided in the contact section.

The rights of users
You may exercise certain rights regarding your information processed by us. In particular, you have the right to do the following: (i) you have the right to withdraw consent where you have previously given your consent to the processing of your information; (ii) you have the right to object to the processing of your information if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent; (iii) you have the right to learn if information is being processed by us, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the information undergoing processing; (iv) you have the right to verify the accuracy of your information and ask for it to be updated or corrected; (v) you have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of your information, in which case, we will not process your information for any purpose other than storing it; (vi) you have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of your Personal Information from us; (vii) you have the right to receive your information in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that your information is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on your consent, on a contract which you are part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.

The right to object to processing
Where Personal Information is processed for the public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in us or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us, you may object to such processing by providing a ground related to your particular situation to justify the objection. You must know that, however, should your Personal Information be processed for direct marketing purposes, you can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether we are processing Personal Information for direct marketing purposes, you may refer to the relevant sections of this document.

How to exercise these rights
Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible.

Privacy of children
We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Information through our Mobile Application or Service. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children\'s Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Information through our Mobile Application or Service without their permission.

If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us through our Mobile Application or Service, please contact us. You must also be at least 16 years of age to consent to the processing of your Personal Information in your country (in some countries we may allow your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf).

Links to other mobile applications
Our Mobile Application contains links to other mobile applications that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other mobile applications or third-parties. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Mobile Application and to read the privacy statements of each and every mobile application that may collect Personal Information.

Information security
We secure information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We maintain reasonable administrative, technical, and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification, and disclosure of Personal Information in its control and custody. However, no data transmission over the Internet or wireless network can be guaranteed. Therefore, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, you acknowledge that (i) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (ii) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and our Mobile Application cannot be guaranteed; and (iii) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third-party, despite best efforts.

Data breach
In the event we become aware that the security of the Mobile Application has been compromised or users Personal Information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, including, but not limited to, security attacks or fraud, we reserve the right to take reasonably appropriate measures, including, but not limited to, investigation and reporting, as well as notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities. In the event of a data breach, we will make reasonable efforts to notify affected individuals if we believe that there is a reasonable risk of harm to the user as a result of the breach or if notice is otherwise required by law. When we do, we will post a notice in the Mobile Application, send you an email.

Legal disclosure
We will disclose any information we collect, use or receive if required or permitted by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, and when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

Changes and amendments
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time in our discretion and will notify you of any material changes to the way in which we treat Personal Information. When changes are made, we will revise the updated date at the top of this page. We may also provide notice to you in other ways in our discretion, such as through contact information you have provided. Any updated version of this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy unless otherwise specified. Your continued use of the Mobile Application or Services after the effective date of the revised Privacy Policy (or such other act specified at that time) will constitute your consent to those changes. However, we will not, without your consent, use your Personal Data in a manner materially different than what was stated at the time your Personal Data was collected.

Acceptance of this policy
You acknowledge that you have read this Policy and agree to all its terms and conditions. By using the Mobile Application or its Services you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Policy, you are not authorized to use or access the Mobile Application and its Services.

Contacting us
If you would like to contact us to understand more about this Policy or wish to contact us concerning any matter relating to individual rights and your Personal Information, you may send an email to meetyourtripals@gmail.com

        ]]></string>
</resources>